

Nguyen Khanh Linh

18/10/1999

S 0903196641

linhnguyen181099@gmail.com

District 10 HCMC

JOB OBJECTIVE

I look forward to working in a professional, dynamic environment to develop myself, perfect more skills, and contribute my creativity and experience to serve the company's common goals and mission. company. - Have experience working as a switchboard operator, telesales or customer consultant. As a meticulous person and a lover of perfection, I desire to create perfection in both life and work.

SKILLS

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF FOREIGN LANGUAGES AND INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (HUFLIT)

2017 _ 2021

Industry: Business Administration

Major: Business administration

WORK EXPERIENCE

VNNF COMPANY LIMITED | 09/2022 - 08/2024

Administrative Officer

- Organize and arrange interviews.
- Drafting official documents and internal notices
- Post articles looking for candidates.
- Monitor and notify interview results to candidates.
- Prepare quotes and order office equipment.
- Check equipment and use for the office.
- Manage employee books and documents.
- Plan birthday parties for members during the month, festivals, and year-end reviews
- Payment and finalization of administrative expenses for the month.
- Receive official dispatches, and send company letters and documents
- Support employees on health insurance and social insurance related issues
- Do other jobs as assigned by superiors.

SHINHAN VIETNAM FINANCE COMPANY LIMITED

12/2021 - 07/2022

Administrative Officer

- Collect and store information about employees, including profiles, contact information, salary and insurance information.
- Handle procedures related to recruiting new employees, including reviewing applications, interviewing candidates and drawing up labor contracts.
- Manage employee training and development programs. Monitor and evaluate employee performance, including holding annual performance reviews.
- Handle issues related to employee benefits, including health insurance, social insurance and related policies.
- Support employees in solving salary, bonus and welfare issues. Human resources

administration plays an important role in maintaining a positive and productive working environment in the company.

- Work closely with other departments within the company to ensure that HR policies and procedures are implemented properly and on time

V.KAUS COMPANY LIMITED | 03/2021 - 07/2021

Intern

- Teamwork and group interaction skills
- Communication skill
- Adaptive skills, easy to integrate into new environments
- Presentation skills
- Recruitment skills
- Profile searching skills
- Photo editing, video editing skills
- Currently learning Korean and Chinese
- Likes running events and has experience running events for brands like Heniken, Tiger...

CERTIFICATE

2019

MOS (Word - Excel)

2021

Google Digital Garage

2021

British Council EnglishScore (516 Score)

- Research and write articles on various topics to promote the company's products.
- Moderate content posted on the company's social media platforms.
- Monitor, advise and answer customer questions.
- Support tasks as assigned by superiors.
- -Receive official dispatches and dispatches and send company letters and documents
- Support printing necessary documents as required by departments. Welcoming customers upon arrival to the company
- Report weekly work to superiors
- Recruitment support

TIEN PHONG COMMERCIAL JOINT STOCK BANK | 02/2020 - 11/2020

Customer Service

- Support and answer customers' questions and complaints about the bank's products and services.
- In charge of tasks related to the bank's customer care activities. Support and answer buyers' questions and complaints.
- Guide customers on how to use the bank's apps, and other customer questions related to accounts or banks.
- Update relevant information and reports to the system.
- Perform other tasks as assigned by Management.

